Tom walked into a library and said, “I’d like a burger, fries, and a large cola.”
Tom走进一家图书馆，说：“我想要一个汉堡、薯条和一大杯可乐。”
The librarian stared at him and whispered, “Sir, this is a library.”
图书管理员盯着他，低声说：“先生，这里是图书馆。”
Tom looked embarrassed.
Tom看起来很尴尬。
He leaned closer and whispered, “Sorry… I’d like a burger, fries, and a large cola.”
他凑近一些，低声说：“抱歉……我想要一个汉堡、薯条和一大杯可乐。”
The librarian sighed.
图书管理员叹了口气。
“We don’t serve food here.”
“我们这里不提供食物。”
Tom nodded seriously.
Tom严肃地点了点头。
“That’s okay.”
“没关系。”
“Then I’ll just eat the book about sandwiches.”
“那我就吃掉那本关于三明治的书。”
“Is it in the delicious section?”
“它在美味区吗？”
The librarian said, “No, but your joke definitely belongs in the fiction section.”
图书管理员说：“不，但你的笑话肯定属于小说区。”